Zankoku na tenshi no you ni
Just like the cruel angel
Shounen yo shinwa ni nare
Young boy, become a legend
2D4U PRESENTS:
Aoi kaze ga ima
Even though the untested breeze...
mune no doa o tataitemo
...taps at the door to your heart
Watashi dake o tada mitsumete hohoenderu anata
You just look solely at me and smile
Sotto fureru mono motomeru koto ni muchuu de
So intent on seeking out that gentle touch
Unmei sae mada shiranai itaike na hitomi
Such innocent eyes, still ignorant of their destiny
Dakedo itsuka kizuku deshou
But someday, you are sure to realize...
sono senaka ni wa
...that upon your back
Haruka mirai mezasu tame
You have the wings with which to fly...
no hane ga aru koto
...towards the distant future
Zankoku na tenshi no teeze
The cruel angel's thesis
Madobe kara yagate tobidatsu
Soon, you will take flight from the windowsill
Hotobashiru atsui patosu de
With your torrent of ardent pathos
Omoide o uragiru nara
If you are to betray our memories
Kono sora o daite kagayaku
You, who embrace these heavens and shine
Shounen yo shinwa ni nare
Young boy, become a legend
Hey, have you seen her yet?
Oh, yeah! Yeah!
Seen who?
You dork, you haven't seen
the foreign girl yet?
Foreign girl?
Yeah, she's in 8th grade, Class A.
She just transferred here last week.
She's hot!
Great Deal
30 yen per picture
Asuka Langley Sohryu
Photo Order Sheet
Her name's Asuka Langley Sohryu,
did you know that?
She's seriously cute.
Since she was raised over there
but born here,
do you think she matured early?
Don't be stupid!
I bet she broke up in Germany,
and she's here in a foreign land
with a heart that can't be mended.
To Miss Sohryu
Oh, man...
Everybody and their brother!
Asuka! Asuka!
They're just ignorant.
Thank you, come again.
At least the pictures don't
reveal her personality.
Hello!
Shinji!
Guten Morgen!
Guten morgen...
Hey, why so gloomy this early?
This is the gorgeous Asuka greeting you!
Look a little more happy about it!
So the other one's here too, isn't she?
Who's that?
What are you, stupid? I'm talking about
the First Child, of course!
Oh, if it's Ayanami...
Hello!
You must be Rei Ayanami,
the pilot of the prototype.
I'm Asuka! Asuka Langley Sohryu.
I'm the pilot of Eva Unit 02.
Let's be good friends!
Why?
Because it'd be convenient, in lots of ways.
If I'm ordered to, I will.
Talk about odd.
I'll say. Are only weirdos chosen
to be pilots?
Have you lost some weight?
Have I?
You must be enduring an unrequited love.
How did you know?
Because...
"A woman with a mole in
the pathway of her tears
is destined to a life full of them."
If you're trying to put a move on me,
I'm afraid you can't.
There's a very scary lady watching us.
Long time no see, Kaji.
It's been a while.
You're actually pretty careless,
aren't you, Kaji?
He's as much of an idiot as ever.
If you're done handing over Unit 02,
hurry up and leave!
I just received orders this morning
that I'll be staying here on loan.
So the three of us can hang out again,
just like we used to.
Who'd hang out with YOU?
Enemy attack?!
We just got this report from the
patrolling battlecruiser Haruna.
"Huge submerged object detected off
Ki'i peninsula. Sending data."
The data has been collated.
Wavelength pattern Blue.
Confirmed to be an Angel.
All personnel, go to
battle stations, Level One.
EPISODE 09
MOMENT AND
HEART TOGETHER
The recent battle severely damaged
the intercept system of New Tokyo-3.
We've only effected 26 percent
of the repairs at present.
And our operational capability for
actual combat is virtually nil.
Therefore, we'll crush the target
in a single blow
at the water's edge, right
before it makes landfall!
Units 01 and 02 will mount an attack
in a series of waves.
In other words, close in and take turns.
Roger.
This sucks. It's my Japanese debut.
Why won't she let me take it out myself?
It can't be helped. That's the strategy.
Let me tell you something,
just don't get in my way!
Why did someone like him get chosen
to be a pilot?
Two against one isn't a fair fight.
I don't like it. Not my style.
We don't have the luxury of choosing
our means to survive.
Here it comes!
Commence attack!
Okay, I'll go first! Back me up!
Back you up?
Ladies first!
Sheesh, don't order me around!
You're the new one!
I can take him!
Amazing!
Well, Third Child?!
A fight should be elegant and without waste.
That's cheating!
Today, at 10:58:15 AM,
Unit 01 was attacked by Target A,
which split from the target
submerged 2 km off Suruga Bay.
At the same time, plus 20 seconds,
Unit 02 was halted by Target B.
We have a comment from
the chair of Project E.
This is pathetic.
This is all your fault! You totally
screwed up my debut battle!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who did something stupid!
Stupid?! Where does a lamebrain like you
get off calling me that?
That's just shameless!
What do you mean?! We got in this trouble
because you were in such a rush to defeat it!
What was that? You look like a drowned rat!
How lame!
At 11:03 AM, NERV abandoned the operation
Like you can talk!
And transferred command to
the UN Secondary Force.
You've humiliated us.
At 11:05 AM, the UN forces made
an attack with an N2 mine.
We'll have to re-draw the map again.
7th Angel A/B
They succeeded in burning off 28%
of the target's structural substance.
Did they kill it?
7th Angel B
7th Angel A
Report:
Department of Investigation Division 2,
Nerv Scientific Investigation Branch
This is merely temporary relief.
A second attack is a matter of time.
At least it bought us time to regroup,
so we got something out of it.
Listen up, you two.
Do you know what your job is?
Piloting Eva.
No! Your job is to defeat the Angels.
Nerv does not exist to make
grotesque displays like this.
Therefore, you two must cooperate.
Why should we?!
Enough already.
Why's everyone so touchy here?
It's because adults don't like
to be embarrassed.
Where's Miss Misato?
Cleaning things up. The person in charge
exists to take responsibility.
Here are the internal protests
and damage reports,
and this is a bill from the UN,
and here you have complaints from
the PR department as well.
Make sure you read them all.
I don't have to read them
to know what they say.
"If you're going to fight, do it here," right?
How insightful.
I don't need them to tell me. I'll do it here
as soon as the topside gets cleaned up.
I'll destroy the Angels without fail.
The Vice Commander is livid.
You'll almost certainly be demoted
if you embarrass him again.
It was a silver lining that
Commander Ikari wasn't here.
If he'd been here, you'd have been fired
before he ever saw these.
So, you brought me an idea
to help save my job, right?
Just one.
You're amazing, Dr. Ritsuko Akagi.
It's good to have kind friends from way back.
Unfortunately, I'm not the one who will be
bailing out my old friend.
This is Kaji's idea.
To my honey
Kaji's?
I'm home! Not that anyone's here,
of course, but...
What is this?!
Don't be so rude!
Those are my personal belongings!
What are you doing here?!
It's more like, why are you still here?
Still here?
You've been dumped for the new model!
Misato will be living with me.
Well, it's the logical choice when you
consider whose abilities are superior.
Although honestly, I'd rather live with Mr. Kaji.
But why are Japanese rooms
so small anyway?
Not even half of my stuff fits!
Shin's Ro
On top of which, why don't the Japanese
have any sense of privacy?
How can they live in rooms without locks?
Unbelievable!
It's because the Japanese way
is to consider the priorities and needs
of others before one's own.
Miss Misato!
Welcome home! Looks like you're
getting along well already.
What do you mean?
This is all preparation for the next operation.
How's that?
The seventh Angel has one
and only one weakness!
A simultaneous two-point attack
on each target's core
while its components are separated.
In other words, an attack by two Evas
with perfectly synchronized timing.
For that, we'll need cooperation and
perfect coordination from you two.
Therefore, I'm having you two live together.
No way!
It's always been said that boys and girls
shouldn't sleep together after age seven!
The Angel is currently restoring itself.
It will begin its second assault in six days,
so there's no time.
But that's crazy!
So here's how to make the crazy possible.
In order for you to master perfect unison,
you'll memorize the attack pattern that's been
arranged to this music.
In six days, as soon as possible.
But I wonder what's happened to Shinji.
He's been gone three days, right?
Hey, there's the class rep.
Two of the three stooges.
Why are you here?
To see how Miss Sohryu is doing.
What about you two?
To see how Ikari's doing.
Why did you stop here?
Yes?
Traitor!
Matching outfits yet again,
in this day and age?!
I can't believe this!
Well, Miss Misato said that Japanese start by
dressing the part, so she made us...
That's filthy, you two!
You're wrong! You're wrong!
Two wrongs don't make a right!
Oh, welcome everybody!
Could ya please explain
what all this's about?
You shoulda told us that to begin with.
So how is the coordination coming?
Well, as you can see...
Are you surprised?!
There's no way I could possibly lower myself
to Shinji's level!
It's just an utterly impossible idea!
Then you give up?
You don't have anyone else, do you?
Rei?
Yes, Ma'am.
Why don't you try?
It looks like I should alter the
operation to pair Shinji and Rei.
No! I can't stand this! I've had enough!
Asuka!
Even the Devil cries sometimes.
Ikari!
Go after her!
You made a girl cry! Take responsibility!
Well...
Don't say anything.
I know.
I have no choice but to pilot the Eva.
I'll do it.
Since it's come to this, I'll show up
both Rei and Misato!
You don't have to show them up or anything.
You're being too easy on them!
You're a man, aren't you?!
For their attack...
on my pride...
I'll pay them back ten times over!
TWO
MORE
DAYS
ATTACK
TOMORROW
Where's Misato?
At work. She called earlier.
She'll be there all night.
So that means we're all alone tonight.
This is the impenetrable Wall of Jericho.
Take one step over this wall
and you're a dead man.
And now, it's time for children to go to bed!
How can the Japanese sleep on the floor?
I can't believe it.
Mama...
You're just a child yourself.
No, somebody will see us.
Who's watching?
Someb...
Honestly! There's nothing
between us anymore.
Don't do that again.
But your lips didn't say no.
Your lips or your words...
Which one should I trust?
There you go.
Thanks.
You're unusually sober today.
Yeah, a little.
Work? Or a man?
A lot of things.
Still in love?
Don't say weird stuff like that!
Who'd want that jerk?!
It may have been a youthful indiscretion,
but I can't believe I was dating a jerk like him.
It's the biggest blemish on my life.
I meant that he may still like you.
Did I scare you?
Why you lousy...
Getting angry only shows I hit a sore spot.
Why not be more honest with
your feelings this time?
Things are different than eight years ago.
It hasn't changed. Not a bit.
Still too immature.
Well, I've got to get to work.
Tomorrow is the big day.
Target has broken through
the final defense line at Gora.
Here it comes!
We won't fail this time!
Deploy your AT fields as soon
as the music starts.
Then stick to the operation.
Got it, you two?
Roger!
The target has entered the mountains.
Full power, maximum speed
from the start, got it?
I know that. We'll finish in sixty-two seconds.
Target entering Ground Zero.
Detach external power cables.
Launch.
Time remaining
Both Evas confirmed operational.
Geez...
This is pathetic.
You jerk! How dare you do that
to my Unit 02?!
What are you talking about?
You're the one who fell on me!
You're the one who lost his timing first!
It's because you're always so out of it!
What were you doing, staying up
so late last night?!
Image training for today's battle!
Liar! I know you tried to kiss me
while I was sleeping!
No fair! You were awake?!
That's awful! I was just kidding,
but it was real?! You kissed me?!
No, I didn't! I stopped!
Pervert! Lech! Fiend! I can't believe you!
It's because you talk in your sleep
and toss and turn so much!
Those kids are embarrassing us again.
TO BE CONTINUED
PREVIEW
The crater of Mount Asama where
an unhatched Angel lies.
Nerv attempts the first capture of an Angel.
A specially-equipped Eva Unit 02
challenges the fires of Hell!
Next episode: "Magma Diver"
And I'll give you more fan service next time!
Magma Diver